PRINSA SINGH

Senior Digital Marketing Manager

\$ 8092755964

@ prinsa.alightsoftware@gmail.com

- alightsoftware.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/prinsa-singh-002937271/
- Siwan Bihar

☆ Digital Marketer"



SUMMARY

I have 3 years of experience in digital marketing, as well as strong leadership skills and a track record of success. I'm currently looking for a position that will allow me to use my extensive skills and experience to find new clients and develop online strategies that will help businesses grow.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Digital Marketing Manager

Alight Software Private limited

I am a highly skilled and experienced digital marketing specialist with a proven track record of success in driving traffic, leads, and sales. I have a deep understanding of the latest digital marketing trends and technologies, and I am passionate about using my skills to help businesses grow. They also provide thought leadership and guidance on emerging technologies and best practices in the field of digital marketing. A digital marketing manager typically has a degree in marketing or a related field, and proven experience in leading and managing successful digital marketing campaigns. They also have strong creative, analytical, and communication skills, as well as a passion for learning new skills and tools. A digital marketing manager can work in various industries and sectors, such as ecommerce, education,

entertainment, finance, health care, media, retail, technology, etc.

Digital Marketing Manager

Alight Software Private limited

苗 2021 - 2023 👂 Siwan Bihar

 digital marketing campaigns, including web, SEO/SEM, email, social media and display advertising. Maintaining our social media presence across all digital channels. Measuring and reporting on the performance of all digital marketing campaigns. The candidate will develop, implement, and manage marketing campaigns promoting the organization's products and services

SEO Specialist

Alight Software Private limited

🗰 2021 - 2023 👂 Siwan Bihar

 I'm a SEO Expert with a successful track record in leading digital marketing strategies & executions. Have capabilities of building Brand/organization digitally in touch with current digital trends in the market. An SEO expert is a professional who knows how to optimize a website for search engines and increase its organic visibility, traffic, and conversions. An SEO expert has a thorough understanding of online research methods, marketing trends, online venues, techniques, and tools that can improve a client's online.

PERSONAL INTERESTS



Become an expert digital marketer"

Work as an SEO Expert



Active Learning

I love reading and learning new things to improve myself and be tuned with dynamically changing world and trends.



Desicion-Making and Time Management

I like to analyse data, find a simple direction and goal, make a plan of actions in order to fit in a deadline, and execute it.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Applications

Maulana Mazhrul Haque Unvercity Patna,Bihar

2023 - Present

Advanced Diploma in Computer Applications

institute

= 2020 - 02/2021

SKILLS

SEO Backlinks	Guest Posting
Lead Generate	Artificial Intelligence
Web Devloper	Link Bulding
Advertising A	Ads Managment
Social Media Managment C#	
HTML CSS	Microsoft Office



www.alightsoftware.com